http://www.logcabinhomes.com/privacy/

Build Your Home With CedarCypressPineThis legal notice and privacy policy applies solely to information collected by The Original Log Cabin Homes website (https://www.logcabinhomes.com). It covers the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing The Original Log Cabin Homes is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this personally identifying information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to fulfill an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.We do not store any personally identifying information online. Any information you transmit to us through any contact forms or email is protected offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Cookies We use browser “cookies” on the LogCabinHomes.com  website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Please note, while our site does not require any log-in to view it, browser cookies may still be created for non-personally-identifying visit information. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (Google Analytics). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. We utilize Google Adwords’ Remarketing to advertise online and, as a result, cookies may be used to serve ads based on past visits to our website.Visitors to LogCabinHomes.com can opt-out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings page. Alternately, you may opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. Sharing We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers (Google Analytics). This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person or corporation.Updates Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via postal mailing address. (P.O. Drawer 1457 • Rocky Mount, NC 27802)About UsHomeLatest NewsletterIn The NewsMission StatementHistoryTradition Meets TechnologyWorldwide DistributionThe American BuffaloCertified Green ManufacturerForest Stewardship Council CertificationBillion Dollar Buying PowerLog Home FinancingPeople PowerPersonal Model & Mill Tour105% Price GuaranteeBetter Business BureauOur ProductMaterials ListMossy Oak® Nativ Living™ Edition Materials ListLog Profiles & Custom JoineryLaminated OptionsWood SpeciesCedar, Cypress or PineEastern White PineWestern Red CedarBald CypressOur HomesFREE Custom Quote RequestFloor PlansCompanion StructuresSmall CabinsMurray Arnott SignaturePhoto TourExterior Photo GalleryInterior Photo GalleryThe DifferenceLay-A-Way Purchase ProgramLimited Lifetime WarrantyPride In ExcellencePrecision MillingTestimonials0% Down PurchaseLog Cabin Homes Vehicle TradeEnergy Performance of Log HomesFire Performance of Log HomesLog Grading ProgramModel Sales CentersRocky Mount, NCSt. Augustine, FLWinston Salem / Greensboro, NCCustomer ServiceCustomer ServiceDesign & BlueprintsSelecting A BuilderBuyer’s GuideBuyer BewareLog CraftersBlogsMurray ArnottMonday Minutes – ArchivesRV CampgroundInfo & ReservationsShows & EventsSchedulePersonal Model & Mill TourReceive InformationOrder Free BrochureGet The iOS App!Community OutreachCommunity OutreachBlackCycle PartnersAcquisitions WantedMossy Oak® LinksMossy Oak® Nativ Living™ EditionMossy Oak® Press ReleaseMossy Oak® StoreMossy Oak® PropertiesNew Listings (5 Offers)  One of our own serving our country SPC T. J. Vesce at Fort Benning, GeorgiaUpcoming EventsConstruction Workshop & Seminar with Model Tour - Greensboro / Winston Salem, NCDecember 12, 2020Construction Workshop & Seminar with Model Tour - St. Augustine, FLDecember 19, 2020Construction Workshop & Seminar with Model Tour - St. Augustine, FLJanuary 09, 2021Construction Workshop & Seminar with Model Tour - Greensboro / Winston Salem, NCJanuary 16, 2021Construction Workshop & Seminar with Model Tour - St. Augustine, FLFebruary 06, 2021Click to see all events! Would you like to request more information?
× Every Original Log Cabin Homes Builder / Dealer Wholesale Materials Package includes the following materials:LOGWALL SYSTEM:All the Builders Series solid 8”X6” random length Bald Cypress precision milled double T&G logs for the exterior walls (first floor) 8ft Nominal Height, Log Homes Council Graded. (Story and One Half models include log siding for second floor exterior walls, Full Two story models include Solid Logs for exterior walls)All the “Bison” lag screws needed to fasten each log courseAll the double row of log course polyfoam insulation sealing tape – “Log Cabin” Log Seal BrandAll the oak joint dowels for butt ends & corner jointsAll the “Log Cabin” log caulking for butt and end jointsWINDOWS:All the Builders Series Insulated Natural Wood Double Hung Thermopane Windows(Low-E)Trapazoid and Fixed Glass (By Owner)Tempered glass when required by national codes where required according to our standard layout.DOORS:All the Builders Series 9 lite over 2-panel or 6 panel metal clad thermo insulated entry doors when illustratedAll the thermo insulated French Patio Swingers when illustratedSECOND FLOOR SYSTEM: (for 50lb. loading)All the 2x conventional second floor joists when applicableAll Second Floor Support Girders when requiredAll second Floor Support Posts when requiredSolid Wood Blocking provided at midspan and over load bearing wall.All the 7/16”OSB Girder and Header filler when requiredROOF SYSTEM:All the stress engineered 2x conventional roof rafters and collar ties or trusses for the roof system depending on design, for 30lb roof loadingAll the 7/16” Structurwood OSB roof decking.All the engineered lumber valley beams when requiredAll the Hip Rafters when requiredAll the 2X Ridgeboard when requiredAll Barge RaftersAll ladder framing and 2X SubfaciaPORCH ROOF SYSTEM: (When Illustrated)4X6 Porch Posts6X8 Carry BeamsAll framing and matching Log Siding for Porch Gable Ends.All 2X Porch RaftersAll Ladder Framing and SubfaciaAll Barge RaftersValley and Hip Rafters when applicable.All the 7/16” Structurwood roof decking.INTERIOR PARTITIONS:All the 2”x4” interior studding for partition wallsAll the 2”x6” plumbing walls8ft Partition walls have precut studsAll top and bottom plates for studwalls2X6 Headers with 7/16 OSB filler for bearing openings2X10 Headers with 7/16 OSB filler for all load bearing openingGABLE ENDS:2X Studding and Framing materials2X Window header with 7/16 OSB filler where requiredMatching Log Cabin SidingSolid Log Gables are OptionalDORMERS: (When Illustrated)All 2X Studding and Framing MaterialsMatching Log Cabin Siding2X Window Headers with 7/16 OSB filler where required2X RaftersValley RaftersDormer HeadersAll the 7/16” Structurwood OSB roof decking.EXTRASAll the “Log Cabin” Building Wrap Protection to protect your Log Home materials during constructionUp to 5 sets of Auto-CAD designed blueprintsFinal Prints to Include: Floor plans, Elevations, Standard Foundation Plans, Roof Framing, 2nd Floor Framing, Building Section, and Standard Detail Sheet.Log Cabin Homes “HOW-TO” construction guideWorldwide Delivery! In Compliance with the 2017 IBC – International Building CodeMany Options and upgrades Available! Log Cabin Homes welcomes any custom quote without obligation. Ask your Representative for details. Heavy Roof and Floor loadings, High altitude, Seismic, Hurricane, Nordic, Tropical and other extreme weather building specifications are available as an upgrade.
CLOSE Every Original Log Cabin Homes Builder / Dealer Wholesale Materials Package includes the following materials:LOGWALL SYSTEM:All the Builders Series solid 8”X6” random length Eastern White Pine precision milled double T&G logs for the exterior walls (first floor) 8ft Nominal Height, Log Homes Council Graded. (Story and One Half models include log siding for second floor exterior walls, Full Two story models include Solid Logs for exterior walls)All the “Bison” lag screws needed to fasten each log courseAll the double row of log course polyfoam insulation sealing tape – “Log Cabin” Log Seal BrandAll the oak joint dowels for butt ends & corner jointsAll the “Log Cabin” log caulking for butt and end jointsWINDOWS:All the Builders Series Insulated Natural Wood Double Hung Thermopane Windows(Low-E)Trapazoid and Fixed Glass (By Owner)Tempered glass when required by national codes where required according to our standard layout.DOORS:All the Builders Series 9 lite over 2-panel or 6 panel metal clad thermo insulated entry doors when illustratedAll the thermo insulated French Patio Swingers when illustratedSECOND FLOOR SYSTEM: (for 50lb. loading)All the 2x conventional second floor joists when applicableAll Second Floor Support Girders when requiredAll second Floor Support Posts when requiredSolid Wood Blocking provided at midspan and over load bearing wall.All the 7/16”OSB Girder and Header filler when requiredROOF SYSTEM:All the stress engineered 2x conventional roof rafters and collar ties or trusses for the roof system depending on design, for 30lb roof loadingAll the 7/16” Structurwood OSB roof decking.All the engineered lumber valley beams when requiredAll the Hip Rafters when requiredAll the 2X Ridgeboard when requiredAll Barge RaftersAll ladder framing and 2X SubfaciaPORCH ROOF SYSTEM: (When Illustrated)4X6 Porch Posts6X8 Carry BeamsAll framing and matching Log Siding for Porch Gable Ends.All 2X Porch RaftersAll Ladder Framing and SubfaciaAll Barge RaftersValley and Hip Rafters when applicable.All the 7/16” Structurwood roof decking.INTERIOR PARTITIONS:All the 2”x4” interior studding for partition wallsAll the 2”x6” plumbing walls8ft Partition walls have precut studsAll top and bottom plates for studwalls2X6 Headers with 7/16 OSB filler for bearing openings2X10 Headers with 7/16 OSB filler for all load bearing openingGABLE ENDS:2X Studding and Framing materials2X Window header with 7/16 OSB filler where requiredMatching Log Cabin SidingSolid Log Gables are OptionalDORMERS: (When Illustrated)All 2X Studding and Framing MaterialsMatching Log Cabin Siding2X Window Headers with 7/16 OSB filler where required2X RaftersValley RaftersDormer HeadersAll the 7/16” Structurwood OSB roof decking.EXTRASAll the “Log Cabin” Building Wrap Protection to protect your Log Home materials during constructionUp to 5 sets of Auto-CAD designed blueprintsFinal Prints to Include: Floor plans, Elevations, Standard Foundation Plans, Roof Framing, 2nd Floor Framing, Building Section, and Standard Detail Sheet.Log Cabin Homes “HOW-TO” construction guideWorldwide Delivery! In Compliance with the 2015 IBC – International Building CodeMany Options and upgrades Available! Log Cabin Homes welcomes any custom quote without obligation. Ask your Representative for details. Heavy Roof and Floor loadings, High altitude, Seismic, Hurricane, Nordic, Tropical and other extreme weather building specifications are available as an upgrade.
CLOSE
Shenandoah
CLOSE
Highland
CLOSE
Blueridge III
CLOSE
Wintergreen III
